Governor's Efficiency Study Commission SR.397
State Archives of North Carolina
- Working Files, SR.397.3; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
  - Transportation, Department of, 17; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Governor's Highway Safety Program, undated; 3977; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Governor's Highway Safety Program)
    - Implementation Progress Reports, 1973-1975; 3978; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Progress Reports)
    - Implementation Status Reports, 1974-1975; 3979; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Implementation Status Reports)
    - Landscaping Plans, 1973; 3980; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Landscaping Plans)
    - Locations and Surveys, undated; 3981; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Locations and Surveys)
    - Mail Inspection, 1972-1973; 3982; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Mail Inspection)
    - Maintenance Personnel Information, undated; 3983; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Maintenance Personnel Information)
    - Maintenance Personnel Standards, 1969-1973; 3984; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Maintenance Personnel Standards)
    - Materials and Tests Department, 1973; 3985; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Materials and Tests Department)
    - Motor Pool Subcommittee, 1973; 3986; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Pool Subcommittee)
    - Motor Vehicles: Administration Office, 1972-1973; 3987; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Administration Office)
    - Motor Vehicles: Common Carrier Tax Division, 1973; 3988; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Common Carrier Tax Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: Data Processing, 1973; 3989; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Data Processing)
    - Motor Vehicles: Driver Education and Accident Records, undated; 3990; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Driver Education and Accident Records)
    - Motor Vehicles: Drivers License Division (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1973; 3991; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Drivers License Division (folder 1 of 2))
    - Motor Vehicles: Drivers License Division (folder 2 of 2), 1970-1973; 3992; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Drivers License Division (folder 2 of 2))
    - Motor Vehicles: Fiscal, 1973; 3993; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Fiscal)
    - Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol, 1972-1973; 3994; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol)
    - Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol Forms and Reports Manual, 1970; 3995; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol Forms and Reports Manual)
    - Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol Policies and Procedures Manual, 1971; 3996; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Highway Patrol Policies and Procedures Manual)
    - Motor Vehicles: Highway Safety Promotion Division, 1973; 3997; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Highway Safety Promotion Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: License and Theft Division, 1973; 3998; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: License and Theft Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: Office of Planning and Research, 1974; 3999; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Office of Planning and Research)
    - Motor Vehicles: Organizational Charts, undated; 4000; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Organizational Charts)
    - Motor Vehicles: Personnel Division, undated; 4001; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Personnel Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: Purchasing Division, undated; 4002; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Purchasing Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: Registration Division, 1972-1973; 4003; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Registration Division)
    - Motor Vehicles: Traffic Records Information, 1973; 4004; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Traffic Records Information)
    - Motor Vehicles: Traffic Safety and Education, undated; 4005; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Motor Vehicles: Traffic Safety and Education)
    - Organizational Charts, undated; 4006; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Organizational Charts)
    - Photogrammetry Department, 1973; 4007; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Photogrammetry Department)
    - Planning, 1972; 4008; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Planning)
    - Plan of Work, 1972; 4009; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Plan of Work)
    - Port Authority, 1972-1973; 4010; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Port Authority)
    - Preconstruction Department, 1973; 4011; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Preconstruction Department)
    - Project Control Department, 1973; 4012; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Project Control Department)
    - Recommendations: Implemented (folder 1 of 2), 1973-1974; 4013; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented (folder 1 of 2))
    - Recommendations: Implemented (folder 2 of 2), 1973-1974; 4014; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented (folder 2 of 2))
    - Recommendations: More Study, 1973-1974; 4015; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: More Study)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973-1978; 4016; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
    - Right of Way, 1973; 4017; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Right of Way)
    - Roadway Design, 1973; 4018; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Roadway Design)
    - Safety, 1972-1973; 4019; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Safety)
    - Safety and Emergency Planning, 1973; 4020; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Safety and Emergency Planning)
    - Secondary Roads, undated; 4021; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Secondary Roads)
    - State Highway Commission: Biennial Report, 1969-1972; 4022; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Biennial Report)
    - State Highway Commission: Data Processing, 1971-1973; 4023; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Data Processing)
    - State Highway Commission: Equipment Department, 1970-1973; 4024; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Equipment Department)
    - State Highway Commission: Equipment Inventory, 1973; 4025; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Equipment Inventory)
    - State Highway Commission: Expenditures, 1971-1972; 4026; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Expenditures)
    - State Highway Commission: Field Investigation Report for Traffic Paint, 1968; 4027; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Field Investigation Report for Traffic Paint)
    - State Highway Commission: Force Account Construction Study, 1973; 4028; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Force Account Construction Study)
    - State Highway Commission: Maintenance Activity (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1973; 4029; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Maintenance Activity (folder 1 of 2))
    - State Highway Commission: Maintenance Activity (folder 2 of 2), 1970-1973; 4030; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Maintenance Activity (folder 2 of 2))
    - State Highway Commission: Minutes, 1972; 4031; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Minutes)
    - State Highway Commission: North Carolina State University Research Coordination, undated; 4032; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: North Carolina State University Research Coordination)
    - State Highway Commission: Pay Item List, 1973; 4033; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Pay Item List)
    - State Highway Commission: Personnel Class and Position Reports, 1973; 4034; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Personnel Class and Position Reports)
    - State Highway Commission: Personnel Information, 1972; 4035; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Personnel Information)
    - State Highway Commission: Planning and Research Maintenance Study Report, 1972; 4036; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Planning and Research Maintenance Study Report)
    - State Highway Commission: Procedures Manual for Data Collection System, 1973; 4037; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Procedures Manual for Data Collection System)
    - State Highway Commission: Purchasing and Central Services Department, 1971-1973; 4038; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Purchasing and Central Services Department)
    - State Highway Commission: Radio Directory, 1973; 4039; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Radio Directory)
    - State Highway Commission: Repair Parts Inventory Statement, 1973; 4040; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Repair Parts Inventory Statement)
    - State Highway Commission: Summary of Maintenance Cost by System, 1972; 4041; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Highway Commission: Summary of Maintenance Cost by System)
    - Traffic Engineering Department (folder 1 of 3), 1971-1973; 4042; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Traffic Engineering Department (folder 1 of 3))
    - Traffic Engineering Department (folder 2 of 3), 1971-1973; 4043; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Traffic Engineering Department (folder 2 of 3))
    - Traffic Engineering Department (folder 3 of 3), 1971-1973; 4044; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Traffic Engineering Department (folder 3 of 3))
    - Traffic Engineering Department, Pavement Marking Report, 1973; 4045; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Traffic Engineering Department, Pavement Marking Report)
  - Treasurer, Department of, 18; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Introduction, 1973-1974; 4046; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Introduction)
    - Recommendations: Implemented, 1973; 4047; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Implemented)
    - Recommendations: In Process, 1973-1974; 4048; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: In Process)
    - Recommendations: Unacceptable, 1973; 4049; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Recommendations: Unacceptable)
  - Universities, 19; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission.
    - Agricultural and Technical College, 1968-1973; 4050; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Agricultural and Technical College)
    - Appalachian State University (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 4051; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Appalachian State University (folder 1 of 2))
    - Appalachian State University (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 4052; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Appalachian State University (folder 2 of 2))
    - Board of Higher Education, undated; 4053; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Board of Higher Education)
    - Board of Higher Education, Statistical Abstract, 1971-1972; 4054; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Board of Higher Education, Statistical Abstract)
    - East Carolina University, 1973; 4055; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University)
    - East Carolina University: Audit Report (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1972; 4056; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University: Audit Report (folder 1 of 2))
    - East Carolina University: Audit Report (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1972; 4057; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University: Audit Report (folder 2 of 2))
    - East Carolina University: Personnel and Position Distribution Report, 1973; 4058; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University: Personnel and Position Distribution Report)
    - East Carolina University: Self-Study (folder 1 of 2), 1972; 4059; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University: Self-Study (folder 1 of 2))
    - East Carolina University: Self-Study (folder 2 of 2), 1972; 4060; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder East Carolina University: Self-Study (folder 2 of 2))
    - Elizabeth City State University: Publications, 1972-1973; 4061; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Elizabeth City State University: Publications)
    - Elizabeth City State University: Self-Study, 1971; 4062; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Elizabeth City State University: Self-Study)
    - Fayetteville State University, 1971; 4063; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Fayetteville State University)
    - Fayetteville State University: Publications, 1971-1973; 4064; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Fayetteville State University: Publications)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1971-1973; 4065; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Central University)
    - North Carolina Central University: Publications (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 4066; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Central University: Publications (folder 1 of 2))
    - North Carolina Central University: Publications (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 4067; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina Central University: Publications (folder 2 of 2))
    - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1971-1974; 4068; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina School of the Arts)
    - North Carolina State University (folder 1 of 2), 1971-1973; 4069; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University (folder 1 of 2))
    - North Carolina State University (folder 2 of 2), 1971-1973; 4070; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University (folder 2 of 2))
    - North Carolina State University: Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1973; 4071; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Agricultural Experiment Stations)
    - North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, 1972; 4072; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service)
    - North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Impact '76 Program, 1972; 4073; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Impact '76 Program)
    - North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Job Descriptions, 1972; 4074; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Job Descriptions)
    - North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Wake County Plan of Work, 1972-1973; 4075; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Agricultural Extension Service, Wake County Plan of Work)
    - North Carolina State University: Industrial Extension Services, 1970; 4076; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Industrial Extension Services)
    - North Carolina State University: Instructions to Architects and Engineers, 1972; 4077; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Instructions to Architects and Engineers)
    - North Carolina State University: Local Task Force, 1973; 4078; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Local Task Force)
    - North Carolina State University: Physical Plant, 1969-1973; 4079; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Physical Plant)
    - North Carolina State University: Report on Audit (folder 1 of 2), 1970-1971; 4080; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Report on Audit (folder 1 of 2))
    - North Carolina State University: Report on Audit (folder 2 of 2), 1970-1971; 4081; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Report on Audit (folder 2 of 2))
    - North Carolina State University: Self-Study, 1973; 4082; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder North Carolina State University: Self-Study)
    - Office of State Personnel Salary Plan Report, 1972; 4083; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Office of State Personnel Salary Plan Report)
    - Pembroke State University (folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973; 4084; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Pembroke State University (folder 1 of 2))
    - Pembroke State University (folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973; 4085; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder Pembroke State University (folder 2 of 2))
    - State Personnel Act Exemptions, 1973; 4086; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder State Personnel Act Exemptions)
    - University of North Carolina at Asheville, 1971-1973; 4087; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Asheville)
    - University of North Carolina, Board of Governors, 1973; 4088; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina, Board of Governors)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1970-1973; 4089; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Administrative Information, 1971-1972; 4090; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Administrative Information)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Annual Commencement, 1972; 4091; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Annual Commencement)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Chemistry, circa 1970; 4092; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Chemistry)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Computer Science, 1971-1973; 4093; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Computer Science)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 1 of 4), 1973; 4094; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 1 of 4))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 2 of 4), 1973; 4095; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 2 of 4))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 3 of 4), 1973; 4096; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 3 of 4))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 4 of 4), 1973; 4097; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Independent Recommendation Reports (folder 4 of 4))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Institute of Government, 1972; 4098; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Institute of Government)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Morehead Planetarium, 1972; 4099; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Morehead Planetarium)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: North Carolina Memorial Hospital (folder 1 of 2), 1973; 4100; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: North Carolina Memorial Hospital (folder 1 of 2))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: North Carolina Memorial Hospital (folder 2 of 2), 1969-1973; 4101; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: North Carolina Memorial Hospital (folder 2 of 2))
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Office of Research Administration, 1971-1973; 4102; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Office of Research Administration)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Personnel Department, 1971-1973; 4103; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Personnel Department)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Personnel and Position Distribution Report, 1973; 4104; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Personnel and Position Distribution Report)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Physical Plant, 1972; 4105; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Physical Plant)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Print Shop, undated; 4106; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Print Shop)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Purchasing, 1972-1973; 4107; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Purchasing)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Security and Parking, 1972; 4108; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Security and Parking)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. N. Smith File, 1972-1973; 4109; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: J. N. Smith File)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Student Affairs, undated; 4110; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Student Affairs)
    - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Student Stores, 1972-1973; 4111; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill: Student Stores)
    - University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 1 of 3), 1965-1973; 4112; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 1 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 2 of 3), 1965-1973; 4113; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 2 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 3 of 3), 1965-1973; 4114; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Charlotte (folder 3 of 3))
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro, 1971-1973; 4115; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro)
    - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Catalog, 1971-1973; 4116; Governor's Efficiency Study Commission. (Folder University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Catalog)